// src/data/germanStates.js

const germanStates = [
  { front: "Baden-Wurttemberg", back: "Stuttgart"},
  { front: "Bavaria", back: "Munich"},
  { front: "Berlin", back: "Berlin"},
  { front: "Brandenburg", back: "Potsdam"},
  { front: "Bremen", back: "Bremen"},
  { front: "Hamburg", back: "Hamburg"},
  { front: "Hesse", back: "Wiesbaden"},
  { front: "Lower Saxony", back: "Hanover"},
  { front: "Mecklenburg-Vorpommern", back: "Schwerin"},
  { front: "North Rhine-Westphalia", back: "Dusseldorf"},
  { front: "Rhineland-Palatinate", back: "Mainz"},
  { front: "Saarland", back: "Saarbrucken"},
  { front: "Saxony", back: "Dresden"},
  { front: "Saxony-Anhalt", back: "Magdeburg"},
  { front: "Schleswig-Holstein", back: "Kiel"},
  { front: "Thuringia", back: "Erfurt"},
];

export default germanStates;